<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Ziang (Danny) Tong</title>
    <link>https://dannytds.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Ziang (Danny) Tong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2023 by Danny Tong.</copyright><atom:link href="https://dannytds.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dannytds.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dannytds.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently in my senior year at the University of Notre Dame, on the track towards a B.S. in computer science with supplementary major in applied computational math and statistics (ACMS).
In school, I&amp;rsquo;m part of the SaNDwich lab in human-computer interaction, directed by Dr. Toby Jia-jun Li and the Visualization lab in computer graphics and scientific visualization, directed by Dr. Chaoli Wang.
In my spare time, I am a video game developer, landscape photographer, and EDM producer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experiences</title>
      <link>https://dannytds.github.io/experiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dannytds.github.io/experiences/</guid>
      <description>Research Generative Models for UX Design Building systems to provide inspirations for UI/UX designers by harnessing the power of generative machine learning models.
Novel View Synthesis without Camera Position Prior Leveraging implicit neural representation (INR) and neural radiance fields (NeRF) to construct novel views without the need for accurate camera position prior.
Social Collaboration in VR Investigated the nuanced way people engage in VR workspace, aiming to mitigate any sense of segregation experienced in the virtual environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://dannytds.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dannytds.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>BMinor Compiler
C, Flex, Bison, ARM Assembly
Peer-to-peer Social Network
Python, TCP/UDP Networking
ViewINR Visualization
JavaScript, React.js
TinDev: a Fullstack Recruiter-Applicant Matchup Platform
JavaScript, Python, Bootstrap, Django, MySQL
Notre Dame Philosophy Library
WordPress, MySQL
Procedual Landmass Generation
C#, Unity</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
